let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which cricketer has scored the most runs at the World Cup?",
        answer: "A. Sachin Tendulkar",
        options: [
            "A. Sachin Tendulkar",
            "B. Kumar Sangakkara",
            "C. Sanath Jayasuriya",
            "D. Ricky Ponting"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who was the first Sri Lankan player to play 100 Tests?",
        answer: "C. S Jayasuriya",
        options: [
            "A. M Jayawardene",
            "B. M Muralitharan",
            "C. S Jayasuriya",
            "D. A de Silva"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In which year were the World Cup matches reduced to 50 overs from the previous 60 overs?",
        answer: "D. 1987",
        options: [
            "A. 1983",
            "B. 1979",
            "C. 1992",
            "D. 1987"    
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who was the first Sri Lankan player to have scored a century and taken 3 wickets in the same ODI match?",
        answer: "D. Aravinda de Silva",
        options: [
            "A. Angelo Mathews",
            "B. Sanath Jayasuriya",
            "C. TM Dilshan",
            "D. Aravinda de Silva"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Who won the first ever Cricket World Cup in 1975?",
        answer: "B. West Indies",
        options: [
            "A. Australia",
            "B. West Indies",
            "C. India",
            "D. England"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "When was the Ashes first played?",
        answer: "C. 1877",
        options: [
            "A. 1872",
            "B. 1882",
            "C. 1877",
            "D. 1887"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the largest cricket stadium in the world?",
        answer: "D. Narendra Modi Stadium",
        options: [
            "A. Eden Gardens",
            "B. Melbourne Cricket Club",
            "C. Lords",
            "D. Narendra Modi Stadium"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How many ways are there of getting out?",
        answer: "C. 10",
        options: [
            "A. 7",
            "B. 8",
            "C. 10",
            "D. 9"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How long is the wicket on a cricket pitch?",
        answer: "A. 22 yards",
        options: [
            "A. 22 yards",
            "B. 24 yards",
            "C. 18 yards",
            "D. 20 yards"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who did England beat in the final of the 2019 Cricket World Cup?",
        answer: "D. New Zealand",
        options: [
            "A. Australia",
            "B. West Indies",
            "C. India",
            "D. New Zealand"
        ]
    },
];